I'm Travis Connelly and I am a state certified fire-fighter.
We've reviewed several safety measures in case of a fire what you should do.
What happens if your clothes catch on fire?
Everyone has heard the old safety rule, stop, drop and roll.
Do you always practice this?
Maybe you should practice this during your fire drill.
It is pretty simple in explanation but you should keep in mind some key factors.
If your clothes catch fire, running around won't help.
You should stop obviously.
When you drop, don't just throw yourself to the ground.
Ease yourself down; you don't want to cause any more injury.
Lay down as far as you can so that you can roll and cover all parts of your body.
Make sure that you roll completely over several times to make sure that everything gets smothered out.